hello I'm Simon Corcoran I'm the founder and creator of
the website alt simon.com I've been teaching IELTS for over
16 years and I wrote a Blog lesson almost every
day on my website for about 10 years I've also
got over a million people following my lessons using my
resources across different platforms and websites online and this is
a message for students in Vietnam who are preparing for
adults to tell you that I've teamed up to work
with pastel The Language School in your country I'm working
with them exclusively and officially now there are many websites
in Vietnam and around the world that have copied my
resources and materials for IELTS without my permission you can't
trust those websites there are even some language schools have
done this you can't trust them either they have had
no permission from me and I haven't been involved with
helping them to use the materials properly but I am
working officially an exclusively with pastel so you can trust
them with putting together a unique set of resources and
lessons for sale students in Vietnam now just to talk
a bit about IELTS and preparation many people are preparing
in the wrong way or have the wrong information about
IELTS their focusing too much on grammar for example and
trying to memorize complex structures that they think will get
them high school or they're looking for some tricks or
shortcuts to help them to help to improve their schools
and these things don't work what you need to do
is study and prepare properly and my Approach is based
on three main pillars for first we need a method
for every aspect of the exam not a secret or
a shortcut or a trick a real method of doing
the exam that works so I teach a method for
every aspect every part of the test the second thing
that I would say is essential the second pillar is
to improve your English language you need to work on
your level of English your particularly your use of vocabulary
and the range of vocabulary English words and phrases that
you are able to use where flexibly and correctly and
finally the third pillar is practice we need to do
realistic exam practice and practice exercises so we can use
the techniques the methods and the English language that we've
been studying and that's how I've been working with pastel
to prepare courses that are based on those three pillars
so if you're preparing for the test and if you're
in Vietnam I highly recommend that you check out puzzles
courses so good luck